What is it?
Regarding what happened before,
I really was in the wrong.
I'm here today to apologize.
I'm sorry.
But this incident has also
exposed flaws in the company's management.
So I've put together a proposal.
Please take a look, President An.
I think we can use this opportunity
to implement reforms.
Weed out the underperformers,
adopt agricultural support measures,
and help qualifying fruit farmers.
You did well.
I'll leave this to you.
But
remember what you said today.
You can hold me to it, Little Uncle.
Auntie Hong!
Bring me a cup of coffee.
Baby.
I want this one.
Okay.
Let me feed you.
Here.
I want some too.
I'll feed you.
Mom!
What are you doing?
He... he...
Who... who is he?
What's the matter?
Stop making such a fuss.
He's your elder.
Wait.
Mom,
do you hear yourself?
What did you just say?
This little bastard is my elder?
Cheng Yan, don't worry.
I'll treat you like my own son.
Me?
You're wearing my clothes,
drinking my supplements,
and...
hugging my mom?
You... get your hands off my mom.
Take them off!
Or I'll mess you up right now!
Honey,
look at him.
Cheng Yan!
That's enough!
Apologize to your uncle right now.
Me?
I...
Apologize to him?
What the hell is he?
I should apologize to him?
No...
It's...
It's like this.
Get him out of this house right now.
It's either him or me in this house!
Him or me!
Out! Out! Out!
Fine.
Then if you won't apologize,
you can leave this house.
Have some more.
Drink up!
It'll make you strong.
I'll drink some too.
So good!
Can you handle it?
Who's taking a cab with me?
I'll take her! I'll take her!
It's fine! Drink!
Stop talking.
Let's go, let's go. Time to go home.
Your car is over there.
Little niece.
What's your grandma doing?
Has she been looking for me?
Nope.
Grandma is preparing for
her boyfriend's birthday.
What are you doing?
Happy birthday to you,
Happy birthday to you!
Honey.
Make a wish.
I hope
I can be with you forever, honey.
Never apart for the rest of our lives.
Let me wish you a happy birthday!
Go to hell!
Go join the dead!
Honey!
Cheng Yan!
Are you hoping I die early?
Mom.
Will you get your head straight?
If you want to have fun,
I'll find you a place.
I'll find you Russians,
or Westerners.
He's just a gold-digging toy boy!
He just wants your money!
Second Uncle.
Calm down.
Grandma might have her reasons.
Your grandma isn't thinking straight.
Are you not thinking straight either?
Are none of you thinking straight?
Honey.
Don't be mad.
I want to be with you forever.
Live together,
die together.
Die together?
Cheng Yan!
You unfilial son!
You just want to anger me to death!
Honey,
I believe you.
Mom.
I'm your own son.
I'm your own flesh and blood!
You don't believe me,
but you believe him?
At your age,
do you still believe that in this world
there are such good men?
He's just scheming for your money!
I think
the one scheming for my money is you!
Cheng Yan,
let me tell you,
if you keep this up,
you won't get a single penny!
Mom,
Mom.
I... I didn't mean that.
I mean,
I'm your own son.
I'll be the one to provide until the end.
Otherwise, will you rely on him?
If you don't break up with this toy boy,
then don't consider me your son anymore!
Perfect.
I'll just act as if
I never had this son.
Today,
I have something to announce to everyone.
I am
pregnant.
I'm going to be a dad!
Madam
Your grandma is pregnant.
Aren't you worried at all?
Grandma is older now.
Pregnancy naturally carries risks.
Sang Luo,
there's no need to pretend with me.
Your grandma is having a little son,
so she won't have time
to care about you, her granddaughter.
Auntie Lin,
do you know what the biggest difference
between the two of us is?
It's that I never covet others' things.
Shen Zhou,
I'm really sorry.
I never expected things to go this way.
Actually, this was just an accident.
If you hadn't sought me out,
the life I've lived recently,
I might never have experienced it.
But this child...
Since this child is coming into the world,
it means we are meant to be.
I gladly accept it.
You're much braver than I imagined.
Sang Luo,
actually, I should thank you.
If it weren't for you donating
bone marrow to my sister,
I'd have lost my only relative.
I owe you a life.
In this world,
every single life
deserves to be treated well.
From today onwards,
I'll shoulder my duties as a father.
Understood.
So I've always wanted to ask you,
are you serious about Old Mrs. Cheng?
We are not made of stone.
How can we not have feelings?
Right?
Sister-in-law.
You're in quite the mood today,
asking to meet me alone.
No wonder a toy boy suddenly popped up.
It was all that damn girl's doing.
It was your dear niece,
Sang Luo.
And that's not all.
Who do you think leaked your scandal?
This niece of yours...
...has done a lot behind your back.
How do you know?
If she really did all this...
I won't let her get away with it.
I'll ask her myself.
Do you have any proof?
You're just going to go?
I...
You're so impulsive.
No wonder you ended up in this state.
If you have an idea, just say it.
Spare me the smart talk.
Brilliant move, sister-in-law.
Did you see the photos on social media?
Old Mrs. Cheng and that man...
That man looks a few years younger...
...than Director Sang.
Right?
He's really good-looking.
Rich people, huh.
Who knows if it's true or not.
Looks like their relationship isn't simple.
What are you looking at?
We were just talking about our weekend plans.
Yeah, yeah.
Director Sang.
Did you see what's on the internet?
What is it?
It's already gone viral across all platforms.
When was it posted?
Just now.
Notify the PR department.
In 10 minutes,
meeting in the conference room.
Speak up, everyone.
Who leaked this?
Right now,
I have the right to suspect each of you.
Including you,
A Xi.
I swear to you,
I have never...
...done anything to betray you.
Just shut your mouth.
Those vows of yours...
...I could make 800 times a day.
Mom,
right now, the Cheng family's reputation...
...is ruined nationwide.
Our Cheng family is getting famous...
...not for our red wine,
...but because of your new romance.
And who introduced...
...this new romance to you?
Sang Luo.
Come clean.
Stop pretending.
Come clean about what?
Coach Shen and I go way back.
Introducing him to Grandma...
...was just to be her coach.
Meeting in private...
...was to ask about Grandma's preferences.
I'm a victim in this photo too!
Second Uncle,
what do you mean, 'daily preferences'?
The photo makes it perfectly clear.
Grandma and granddaughter after one man!
What can one photo prove,
Second Uncle?
What can it prove?
You can't even explain this clearly.
What do you think it proves?
Explain yourself.
What was your real purpose in contacting him?
Are you after my mom's fortune?
Condemning Sang Luo over a single photo...
...is too hasty.
I've already sent someone...
...to delete the post.
This kind of rich family gossip...
...is just for everyone's entertainment.
It won't cause any actual harm.
Sang Luo,
it's not that we don't believe you.
It's mainly because...
...you're new to the Cheng family.
Even if Coach Shen...
...wanted to know your grandma's habits...
...to take care of her...
...daily life after pregnancy,
asking anyone of us sitting here...
...would make more sense than asking you.
I definitely couldn't go to you.
A Xi would get worried.
If I went to Cheng Yan,
he would beat you up.
Mom,
there... there's a question I have.
Ever since this woman named Sang Luo
came to our Cheng family,
look at how many things have happened.
My poor sister
is now in a nursing home.
Sister-in-law
almost had a miscarriage.
And then there's Dongdong.
One minute he's falling into the pool,
the next he's falling down the stairs.
Every single one
of these incidents, when did they happen?
If you ask me, she's a Jinx.
Not only is she a Jinx,
she also brought this thing in.
Kick them all out.
Give our Cheng family some peace and quiet.
Sang Luo,
since this child is coming into the world,
it means we're meant to be.
I gladly accept it.
From today onwards,
I'll shoulder my duties as a father.
All right.
Then let me tell you
about some of Grandma's daily habits.
Grandma drinks bird's nest every night.
I'm sorry, darling.
I misunderstood you.
It's okay, A Xi.
I told you,
I would never do anything to betray you.
We originally planned to use Shen Zhou
to make their lives miserable.
I didn't expect
Cheng Yan and Lin Wanmei to outsmart us.
But if we look at it from another angle,
bringing these filthy schemes
out into the open
might not be a bad thing.
You're right.
You mean,
An old tree blossoming is good for us?
Yes.
Sang Luo,
when this is all over,
come back to Korea with me.
Let's talk about it later, Yi Kai.
I haven't decided yet.
What's wrong?
You can't bear to part with Cheng An?
It's getting late.
I should head back now.
I'll walk you out.
This is far enough.
Oh, you.
Bundle up, it's getting cold.
Get some rest.
Look how exhausted you've been.
A Luo.
I really want
you to come back to Korea with me.
Think it over.
I'll think about it.
What are you doing?
I'm your Little Uncle.
Dating
requires an elder's permission.
Are you crazy?
Right, right, right.
A little lighter.
Okay.
This is very comfortable.
Empress Dowager
Mom,
I
personally brought my brother's
test report over here.
As if you'd be so kind.
I thought you disowned me as your mother.
Mom,
I've thought it through, you know.
I figured,
as long as parents are happy,
isn't that their children's greatest joy?
Besides, I'll be a big brother soon.
I must take on a brother's duties.
So what does the test report say?
Let me read it to you.
This test report says
that the fetus has a
relatively high risk of Down syndrome.
It suggests...
Oh my, Mom.
Th-th-this Down syndrome,
doesn't that mean he'll be an idiot?
Look,
I was prepared to be a big brother,
but I wasn't prepared
to be a big brother to an idiot.
Darling.
You have such good genes,
and had so many healthy children.
This... this...
How could you have an idiot?
Not exactly.
Our Cheng family's genes
are indeed quite excellent.
But your genes...
Besides,
for older mothers,
the risk of giving birth is already
extremely high.
Hundreds of times higher.
Shut your mouth.
I'll shut up, I'll shut up.
Mom,
let me state my stance first.
Our Cheng family has a vast fortune.
Raising an idiot is no problem.
As long as you're ready for the disgrace,
I'll provide until the end for my brother.
What are you all talking about?
It's so lively in here.
Luo Luo.
It's fine.
Grandma,
I heard that
Down syndrome screening often has errors.
Why don't I find a few more hospitals
and we get a second opinion?
Why are you being so unreasonable?
Your grandma is advanced in age.
Going to several hospitals for checkups...
Wouldn't that be exhausting for her?
Besides,
do you want the Cheng family
to lose face before the whole world?
Second Uncle is right.
I didn't think this through.
In that case,
let's just stay at this hospital
and do the test one more time.
What do you mean, "one more time"?
I told you it's exhausting.
How could a report I got myself be wrong?
Second Uncle,
I just want to play it safe.
Hospitals making mistakes on test reports
is actually quite common.
Cheng Yan,
are you sure there's no problem
with this report?
I picked it up myself.
There's no way there's a problem.
Grandma...
What is it?
Look at this part with your name.
Mom, Mom, Mom!
I just thought giving birth is exhausting,
and dangerous.
That's why I changed your name on it!
Great. Just great.
You even dared to deceive me.
I... I'll get going now.
Get some rest!
Alright, alright.
Darling,
calm down.
Don't upset the baby.
As long as the baby
is healthy, that's all that matters.
Right?
He's just...
just an...
idiot.
Calm down.
Grandma,
here.
I stewed some bird's nest for you.
You're such a good child.
Try it.
It's delicious.
Grandma misunderstood you.
Grandma,
what are you talking about?
Harmony is what matters most in a family.
But I went back and thought about it.
Everyone argued so fiercely that day.
Actually, setting aside the news for now,
and who exactly exposed it.
With the current public opinion,
people don't seem very accepting.
Including the company's shareholders
and partners.
Well...
What are you suggesting then?
Grandma, you've weathered many storms,
so you're not afraid of this gossip.
But have you thought about this child?
After he's born,
what will others think of him?
This child is a gift from heaven,
and the fruit of your love with Coach Shen.
Grandma, you definitely want him
to grow up happy, right?
So, after much deliberation,
I've come up with an idea.